abroadeducation.com.np 2018-12-28

# Abroad Education Privacy Policy

**ABROADEDUCATION WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

Protecting your privacy online is a main concern at WebNetworks. The following Abroad Education privacy policy informs how we respect your privacy and protect any information you may provide us while visiting our site or utilizing any of our services.

Abroad Education allows full access to our online information free of charge and without requiring any registration. Users may opt to register with Abroad Education. We don't collect any personal information when someone simply visits our websites.  This information is kept confidential and will never be passed to a third party, unless this is required (1) to enforce our Terms and Conditions, (2) by law, (3) to defend us in any legal action, (4) to protect our property.

 **What information is collected**

Information collected may include, among other things, your name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number and other information about yourself.

 **How information is collected**

All personal information is gathered directly from users through online registration forms and signup sections. Only you can modify your profile once it has been created. In case of sign up for the subscription of free newsletters published by Abroad Education only email addresses of users interested in subscription of newsletters is collected and user can change their email address or unsubscribe the newsletter if they are no longer interested in it.

Personal information collected about you may be utilized for the following purposes:

  1. To provide information or services you have requested;
  2. Servicing your account;
  3. Improving our services;
  4. Developing and/or having you informed of additional information/products or services we think will be of interest to you;
  5. Answering questions you may have.

**Aggregate Information about our users**

We routinely gather information about the use of our web sites by all of our users collectively.  We do record general information about each page request, including IP address, the URL of the page requested, the URL of the referring page (if any), the date and time of the request, and the agent (browser) used, when our servers are busiest. This information is used to diagnose problems with our server, establish statistics and to administer our Web site. This information also helps us to improve our services and to evaluate our marketing efforts. We only use such data anonymously and aggregately.

 **Information protection and security**

When you submit your information to AbroadEducation, whether it is your name, address, email or phone number, we do our utmost to ensure that information is protected against loss, misuse, alteration, destruction or unauthorized access. AbroadEducation uses standard encryption tools such as SSL (Secure Socket Layer) to help protect your personal information and to keep information collected secure.

> _Encryption can be used after your data has left your internal system. Encryption renders your data unreadable using a mathematical formulae known as the key. Your data is turned back into readable form, i.e. deciphered, by applying the correct key._

Due to the nature of this technology, there is always a remote danger of information interception no matter what barriers are in place.

Our system does provide for profiles to be sent via un-encrypted email, and may be susceptible to intercept at this point.

Employees within Abroad Education. with access to your information provided are instructed to utilize such information only in adherence to this Privacy Policy. Employees who utilize information for any reason other than the reasons stated within this policy may be subject to reprimand or even legal proceedings.

Our web sites also contain links to other sites. The privacy policies of linked sites may differ from those of Abroad Education.

 **Contact details**

If you would like to contact us for information on any of our services, information on our privacy policy, or for any reason relating to our website, please email us at: info@abroadeducation.com.np 

**AbroadEducation Advertising Policy**

AbroadEducation has partnered with third-party advertising agencies like Google Adwords Program to display advertisements throughout the AbroadEducation.com.np network. These advertisements help us generate revenue to pay for our servers and staffs. While displaying advertisements, the third-party advertisement programs that we use may create some cookies in your system to track your online behavior. Tracking your online behavior allows advertisement providers to serve you the advertisements that are relevant to you. 

AbroadEducation reserves the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Policy statement at any time.
